Finding aid to the Classes of 1879-1890 records CA.MS.01023
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1890 Records, 1886-1975; 4 boxes (1 linear ft. and 8 linear inches)
  - Class of 1890: Cravath, Elizabeth Northway (Correspondence), 1942-43; 1953; undated (Box 1453, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1890: Cravath, Elizabeth Northway (Photographs), 1889; undated (Box 1453, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1890: Day, Harriet Burr (Photographs), undated (Box 1453, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1890: Dodge, Caroline Louise (Photographs), 1889 (Box 1453, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1890: Elmer, Edith, 1889; 1899; 1903; 1910; 1919; 1924; 1928; 1935; 1938-40; 1945; 1975 (Box 1453, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1890: Foley, Margaret Baker (Photographs, etc), 1921-22; 1930; undated (Box 1453, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1890: Goodale, Dora Read, 1906-07; 1917; 1942 (Box 1453, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1890: Greene, Anna Maria, undated (Box 1453, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1890: Hall, Anna Bond (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1453, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1890: Hardwick, Rose Standish (Photographs, etc), 1896; 1912; 1915-16; 1939; undated (Box 1453, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1890: Hoblitt, Margaret Smith (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1890: Holt, Ellen, 1886-87; 1920; 1940; 1957; 1960-61; undated (Box 1454, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1890: Holt, Ellen (Photographs), 1889; undated (Box 1454, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1890: Homans, Susan Manning, 1933; 1953; undated (Box 1454, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1890: Huffman, Mary Lucy, 1935 (Box 1454, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1890: James, Gertrude (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1890: Jenkins, Anna Spaulding (Box 1454, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1890: Lamont, Lucy (Diary), 1886-1888 (Box 1454, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1890: Lathrop, Anna Barrow (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1890: Miner, Frances Manwaring, 1886-87; undated (Box 1454, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1890: Moodey, Cornelia Chapin, 1908 (Box 1454, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1890: Phillips, Maud (Box 1454, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1890: Robinson, Mary Clemant, 1943 (Box 1454, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1890: Seabury, Maria Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1890: Sherrill, Ruth Dakin, 1891 (Box 1454, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1890: Sprague, Leonora Woodruff (Photographs) (Box 1454, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1890: Sumner, Caroline Louise (Class notes, Bible Lectures), 1886-90 (Box 1454, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1890: Sumner, Caroline Louise (Photographs), 1915; 1940; undated (Box 1454, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1890: Thayer, Mary Vining, 1923; undated (Box 1454, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1890: Thomson, Lucy Doolittle (Photographs), 1889; 1943; undated (Box 1454, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1890: Walston, Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1890: Wiggin, Pauline Gertrude (Box 1454, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1890: Willard, Mary Frances (Letters), 1888; 1916; 1961 (Box 1454, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1890: Willard, Mary Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1454, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1890: Wilson, Ella May, undated (Box 1454, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1890: Wonson, Alice Manton, undated (Box 1454, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1890: Woodruff, Agnes Lloyd, undated (Box 1454, Folder 27)